乔伊 快说啦
Come on, Joey!
瑞秋 我知道的部分昨晚都告诉你了
Rach, I told you everything I knew last night.
摩妮卡和钱德搞在一起又怎样
It's not that big a deal. So Monica and Chandler are doing it.
你居然这么说
I cannot believe you would say that!
抱歉 摩妮卡和钱德在"做爱"
Sorry. Monica and Chandler are "making love."
不是啦 我是说这是大事耶
No, I mean, come on. This is a huge deal!
我想知道细节 是谁先吻谁的?
I need more details. Who initiated the first kiss?
不知
I don't know.
他跟她在一起时浪漫吗?
Is he romantic with her?
不知
I don't know.
他们相爱吗?
Are they in love?
- 不知   - 噢
- I don't know.     - Ugh.
你什么都不知道
You don't know anything.
- 我知道件事   - 什么事?
- Oh! I know one thing.     - What?
他们在这张沙发上做过
They did it right there on the couch.
(中央咖啡厅)
- 嘿 罗斯   - 嗯
- Hey, Ross.     - Yeah.
阿甘 给我一个英式松饼
Gunther, could I have a scone, please?
想听好消息吗?
Want to hear some good news?
我认识的某人要结婚了
Someone I know is getting married.
婚礼是最开心的场合 对了 那人是我的前妻艾蜜莉
Yeah, weddings are happy occasions. Oh, by the by, it's my ex-wife, Emily!
真抱歉
Sorry, man.
- 你的英式松饼   - 谢谢 阿甘
- Here's your scone.     - Thanks, Gunther.
谢谢
Thanks.
什么白痴英国点心
Stupid British snack food!
那是情绪管理课教的吗?
Did they teach you that in anger management?
我有个办法 你就这么想
You know what might help deal with it? Think of it this way.
你和艾蜜莉已经过去了 你不能对过去的事生气
You and Emily are in the past. You can't be mad about the past.
你还气我们跟法国买土地吗?
Are you still mad about, you know, the Louisiana Purchase?
- 菲比 没有人在气那个    - 没错 因为已经过去了
- I don't think anybody's mad about that.     - Exactly! Because it's in the past.
那个有人要吃吗?
Anybody going to eat that?
我们盛装参加公司宴会耶 是在庆祝什么?
Look at us all dressed up for the party. What are we celebrating?
圣诞晚会剩了不少酒
We had a lot of liquor left over from the Christmas party.
真好 这里没有我们的朋友
I think this is cool. None of our friends are here.
我们可以公开 不必躲躲藏藏
We can be a real couple. We don't have to hide.
- 没错 我可以这样  - 喔
- I know. I can do this.     - Ooh.
而我可以这样
And I can do this.
- 我们不能那样   - 我们不能那样
- We can't do that.     - We can't do that.
嘿 宾 哈哈哈
Hey, Bing! Ha-ha-ha.
哇哦 这位美女是谁 怎么跟你在一起?
Whoa! Who's the pretty lady, and what is she doing with you?
哈哈哈 我也这样问自己 这是摩妮卡
Ha-ha-ha! I ask myself that very question. This is Monica.
- 我上司道格 道格 这是摩妮卡   - 幸会
- My boss, Doug. This is Monica.     - Hi, nice to meet you.
- 这是我老婆卡拉   - 很高兴认识你
- Hi! This is my wife, Kara.     - Nice to meet you.
- 宾   - 好了
- Bing!     - Okay!
你听到公司找新法律顾问公司 的消息了吗?
Did you hear about the new law firm working for us?
- 没有   - 杜塔 片达 豪伊事务所
- No, sir.     - Yeah, Dewey, Cheatem & Howe.
我们去喝个痛快
Come on, let's go drink our body weight.
- 那是什么？ - 什么？
- What was that?      - What?
你刚才发出的声音
That noise you made?
- 那是我的工作笑   - 你的工作笑？
- Oh, that was my work laugh.     - Your work laugh?
相信我 想熬过这场派对 你也得编出一个来
If you're going to survive this party, you have to come up with one too.
- 好 看我的   - 好
- All right. Check me out.     - Okay.
他说 "30块钱 跟城里一样"
He says, "$30, Father. Same as in town." Ha!
昨晚公司的人都好喜欢你
Hey, everybody at work loved you last night.
- 真的？ - 而且他们因为你…
- Really?     - And they like me more...
而更喜欢我
...just because I was with you.
你弥补了不少乔伊造成的伤害
You repaired a lot of the damage from when they met Joey.
道格还找我们打网球 他出了公司还没理过我
Doug wants us to play tennis. He's never talked to me outside of work.
除了在脱衣舞夜总会那次
Except for that time at that strip club.
脱衣舞教堂
Strip church.
- 我要去找支球拍    - 你不是有支？
- I'm gonna go try to find a racket.     - I thought you had one.
本来有 后来被乔伊 拿去中央公园对着大石头打…
I used to, but then Joey thought it'd be fun to go to Central Park and hit rocks...
石头
...at bigger rocks.
- 瑞秋 你有网球拍吗？ - 嘿
- Hey, Rach, do you have a tennis racket?     - Hey.
我借给乔伊就没拿回来过
Oh, um, I lent it to Joey and I've never gotten it back.
祝你好运
Okay, good luck with that.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Ahem. Hey.     - Hey.
你好吗?
What's up?
你怎么来了?今天不是要盘点
What are you doing here? I thought you had inventory.
没错 但我决定午休久一点
Well I do, but I decided I'd take a long lunch...
陪陪我的朋友摩妮卡
...and spend some time with my friend, Monica.
我们现在都不谈心了
You know, I feel like we don't talk anymore.
你好吗?
How are you?
有什么新变化?
What is new with you?
呵 额…
Heh, um...
不多 工作很顺利
Not much. Um, work's good.
我们不必聊工作 什么都可以聊
We don't have to talk about work. We could talk about anything.
好吧
Okay. Um...
这样吧
Hey! You know what?
我们来聊感情的事
Let's talk about relationships.
- 好 你最近怎样？ - 没人追
- Okay. What's going on with you?     - Nothing.
该你
You go.
我原本觉得银行有一个人很帅
Well, I... There was this guy at the bank that I thought was cute.
现在不觉得了
Um, but I don't anymore.
真精彩
Wow, that's, uh, juicy. Ahem, um...
不过我确实很忙
You know what? I actually do have a lot of work to do.
你确定没别的了?
You're sure there's just not anything else?
确定 你有什么事想说吗?
Yes, I'm sure. Is there something you want to talk to me about?
没有
No.
我…
I...
有也不告诉你
If there was, I wouldn't tell you.
好 然后呢?
Okay, then what happened?
额 噢
Uh, oh! Aw.
额 额
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
待会才轮到你
Ah-ah, you'll get your turn.
- 菲比 在干什么？ - 没什么
- Hey, Pheebs. What's going on?     - Hey. Nothing.
待会再继续
This is not over.
- 糟糕   - 怎么了？
- No, no, no!     - What?
我熬了一整晚写信骂艾蜜莉
Ugh, I was up all night writing this really nasty letter to Emily.
原本写得很好 现在沾满了…
It was perfect, and now it's all covered in...
谢了
Actually, thanks!
可以去看电影了吗?
All right! Everybody ready to go to the movies?
我想我不去了
Uh, actually, I think I'm gonna skip it.
- 你不去？ -对 我要留下来看书
- Really?     - I'm gonna stay and read my book.
我现在只想静一静
I just want to be alone right now.
你真的不去?
Oh. Sure you don't want to come?
汤姆·汉克斯 梅格·莱恩 写信什么的
Tom Hanks, Meg Ryan. They get mail and stuff.
- 我还是不去了   - 好吧
- That's okay, Joe.     - All right.
菲比我们走
Let's go, Pheebs.
好嗯
Oh, God!
宾
Bing!
- 额   - 啊哈
- Unh!     - Aah!
赢了
Game!
说真的 你的搭档真是快狠准
Yeah, I gotta tell you, that partner of yours is a real tiger.
你还好吗?
Are you all right?
我们喝口水
We'll just get a little sip of water.
我今天很猛吧?
Am I on fire today or what?
那两只肉鸡已经烤好 等着被切来吃了
Those birds are browned, basted and ready to be carved.
别激动 网球名将
Okay, easy, Martina.
我觉得下一场应该让他们赢
I think we should let them win the next game.
对不起 你刚说的话我听不懂
I'm sorry, I don't understand what you just said.
让他们赢一场
Let them win one.
你疯了吗?他们任我们宰割 你看他们
Are you crazy? We own those two. Look at them!
他喘不过气来 她在吃药
He can't even breathe, and she's popping pills.
你根本不给他们机会
You're not giving them a chance.
他们有球拍不是吗?
They have rackets, don't they?
宾 我想打完这场就收了
Uh, Bing, I think we're gonna make this the last game.
了解 我求之不得
Yes, sir. Put me out of my misery.
你真的没打过职业?
Are you sure you never played pro? Ha-ha-ha.
拜托让他们赢
Please let them win.
我顶多只能把战力降到95%
I'll take it down to 95 percent, but that's the best I can do.
- 糟糕 漏掉了   - 我来
- Oopsie! Missed it!     - I got it!
好球
Nice shot.
我来
I got it!
出界
Long!
你居然让他们赢
I can't believe you let them win.
至少你把不爽掩饰得很好
Yeah, well, at least you hid your feelings well about it.
- 我很沮丧   - 这是我的球拍
- I was frustrated.     - It was my racket.
是你让我沮丧
I was frustrated with you!
如果没输那场球 他们也不会找我们去吃饭
If we hadn't lost, they would never have invited us to dinner tomorrow.
我最困扰的是…
What bothers me...
你在他们身边整个人都变了
...is how different you act around them.
故意输球 工作笑
The throwing the tennis games, the fake laugh...
"回头见 宾" "不回头就不见"
...the "See you later, Bing!" "Not if I see you first, Doug!"
我不喜欢工作的钱德 那家伙是个狗腿
I don't like "work Chandler." The guy's a suck-up.
因为你这些话…
You know what? Because you said that...
我晚上不跟你玩了
...I'm not putting out tonight!
绝对有问题 我哥从来不彻夜不归
Something's wrong. My brother does not stay out all night.
也许应该去看看垃圾槽
Maybe we should check the trash chute.
罗斯挤不进垃圾槽
Ross couldn't fit down the trash chute.
没错 就差那么一点点
That's right. He almost could.
所以我之前卡住过
Which is exactly how I got stuck there.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey!     - Hey.
天哪
Oh, my God!
你死哪去了?
Where the hell have you been?
就是去外面了
Just, you know, out.
外面 天哪 我们怎么没去那里找
Oh, out! God, I don't know why we didn't think to check there.
你都在做什么?
What were you doing?
我先去喝酒 然后…
I, uh, went to a bar and then...
就晃了一下
...I just, uh, walked around for a while.
你整夜一个人在外面乱逛？
You walked around all night in the city by yourself?
他嘿咻了
He hooked up!
他跟某人嘿咻了
He hooked up with someone.
我不必回答你们的问题 我是个大人
I don't have to answer your questions. Okay? I'm a big boy.
爱怎样就怎样
I can do whatever I want.
他嘿咻了
He hooked up!
聊聊她嘛
Tell us about her!
罗斯 你把围巾掉在…
Ross, you left your scarf...
你们好
Hey, you guys.
好…
Okay. Okay.
好 我知道你们在想什么 但钱德在叶门
I know what you all are thinking, but Chandler is in Yemen.
我还年轻 我有需求 我不能等一辈子
I'm a young woman. I have needs. I can't wait forever.
我也是这么想的
Yeah, no, that's what I was thinking.
所以我求求你们 在批评我之前先想一下
So I'm asking you, please just take a moment before you judge me.
没有人在批评你
Oh, nobody's judging you.
喔
Oh.
好 你 天时地利人和先生
Okay, you, Mr. Right-place-at-the-right-time...
跟我联络
...call me.
我知道你们要说什么
Okay, look, I know what you guys are going to say.
你们的孩子会毛茸茸的
You two would have very hairy children.
我不知道你会说那个
I didn't know you'd say that.
罗斯 珍妮丝耶
Ross! Janice?
等一下 等一下…
All right. Hold on, hold on, hold on.
这是罗斯
This is Ross. Okay?
他是我们的朋友 他显然是疯了
He's our friend. He obviously went crazy.
脑筋秀逗了
He obviously lost his mind.
没那么夸张 好吗? 珍妮丝和我有很多共同点
I didn't lose my mind, okay? Janice and I have a lot in common.
我们都离过婚 我们都有小孩
We've both been divorced. We both have kids.
你真的要再见她?
Are you going to see her again?
- 别影响他   - 我确实要再见她
- Don't put ideas in his head!     - I am gonna see her again.
你看啦 菲比
Damn it, Phoebe!
我要说出一件我没坦承过的事
I have to tell you something that I've never admitted.
高中时我知道你喜欢詹姆法洛 但我还是跟他上了床
In high school, I made out with James even though I knew that you liked him.
哇 说出来的感觉真好 好 该你了
Wow! That feels so good to get off my chest. Okay, you go.
- 该我了？ - 什么意思？
- My turn? What are you talking about?     - Ugh.
摩妮卡
Monica...
我知道你和钱德的事
I know about you and Chandler.
什么?
What?
我那天听到你们在讲电话
I overheard you on the phone the other day.
你说"我会告诉瑞秋 我要花两个小时洗衣服"
You said, "I'll tell Rachel I'm doing laundry for a couple of hours."
他说"洗衣服? 那是我的新绰号吗?"
And he said, "Laundry? Is that my new nickname?"
然后你说"不是
And you said, "No.
你明知你的绰号是大鹏"
You know what your nickname is, Mr. Big."
这个嘛…
Well, heh...
原来你正在写剧本
Sounds like you're writing yourself a little play there, Rach.
记得把结局告诉我
Wow, I... Let me know how that one turns out.
我不知道 因为我吓到把电话挂掉了
I wouldn't know because I got so freaked out I hung up the phone.
如果你听完
Well, if you had kept listening, ha-ha-ha...
你会听到我是叫他大…
...you would have heard me call him Mister Big...
碉堡    - 什么？
...ot.     - What?
大碉堡
Mr. Bigot.
哈哈 他喜欢讲碉堡的笑话
Ha, ha. He tells the most racist jokes.
好 所以就这样
All right. So that's it.
你是说你和钱德之间没什么
You're telling me there's nothing going on between you and Chandler?
我和钱德?
Me and Chandler?
- 拿出20元来   - 好
- Put your $20 down.     - Okay.
先找到零食的赢
First one to find the tasty treat wins.
- 好吗？ - 好
- Okay? All right.     - Mm-hm.
请参赛者从休息室出场
Let's get the contestants out of their isolation booths.
他们出场了
And they're off!
哇哦
Whoa.
别挡住我的参赛者 栽判
Get your foot off my contestant! Judge?
裁判判定没有违规
Judge rules no violation.
啊
Agh.
- 你们好   - 嗯
- Hey, guys.     - Yeah.
说也奇怪 我今天跟珍妮丝过得很开心
It's so weird to say this, but I just had a great date with Janice.
- 什么？ - 真的假的？
- What?     - Are you serious?
没错 我跟她诉说近来的惨事
Yeah. I opened up to her about all the terrible stuff that's been happening to me.
我说了好几个小时
I mean, I talked for hours.
有人专心…
It is amazing...
听你倾诉的感觉真好
...to have someone give you such focused attention.
那你何必找她 你有我们
You don't need Janice for that. You've got us.
- 甲鸟子找到花生酱饼干了   - 不
- And the duck gets the Nutter Butter!     - No! Agh!
那不是花生酱饼干 那是一颗馄饨
That's not a Nutter Butter. That's an old won ton!
裁判判定
Judge rules...
是花生酱饼干  - 额
...Nutter Butter.     - Ugh.
- 真难判   - 是啊
- Tough call.     - Yeah.
说真的 我们应该支持克林顿总统
Seriously, I strongly believe that we should all support President Clinton...
和她的老公比尔
...and her husband, Bill.
你们的咖啡要怎么上?
So how do you like your coffee?
- 我不要 谢谢   - 我要点点糖
- None for me.      - Just a little bit of sugar.
那就让摩妮卡把指头伸进去
I'll have Monica stick her finger in it.
应该就会甜了
That ought to sweeten it up.
- 你那样笑怎么不会头痛？ - 久了就习惯了
- How does that not give you a headache?     - You get used to it.
我不觉得我会习惯
I don't think that I can.
我以后就不用这套了
Maybe this will be it for me on the work things.
老板说笑我就笑 这有什么吗?
So I laugh at my boss's jokes. What's the big deal?
如果能跟我尊敬的男友在一起
I'd rather not hang out with this work-weasel guy...
我干嘛陪一个没尊严的马屁精
...when I could be with my boyfriend, who I actually respect.
嗯
Oh.
啊 呵
Ah, heh.
我得为卡拉煮的咖啡道歉
I gotta apologize for Kara's coffee.
如果它去打架
I'd feel sorry for it if it got in a fight.
连自己都保护不了
It's not strong enough to defend itself. Ha-ha-ha!
你听到我的话了吗?
Hear what I said?
什么?
What?
那个笑话啊 你是怎么了?
It's a joke, Bing. What's the matter with you?
我只是觉得不好笑
Well, I just didn't think it was funny, sir.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
- 我只是…   - 亲爱的
- Well, I just...     - Honey?
我觉得你没听懂
I just don't think you understood the joke.
- 是吗？ - 是啊
- Really?      - Yeah.
很好笑耶 你一定是没听懂
I mean, it was really funny. I just don't think that you got it.
卡拉煮的咖啡很稀
Heh, you see, Kara's coffee is weak-tasting.
但道格是在暗示它很虚弱
But what Doug did was imply that it was weak physically.
- 现在你懂了吗？ - 我懂了
- You get it now, honey?      - I think I do!
- 谢谢你   - 我觉得你需要解释
- Thank you, Monica.     - I thought you could use the help.
哈哈哈
Ha-ha-ha.
咖啡打架
Coffee in a fight!
瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
我可以在这里看漫画吗?
You mind if I read my comic books in here?
当然可以 怎么了?
Sure. Why?
钱德和摩妮卡在一起 我很难专心
Chandler and Monica are over there. It's kind of hard to concentrate.
什么?她刚打来说她要加班
What? She just called and said she was going to be working late.
她一直骗我
She keeps lying to me.
够了 我现在就过去揭穿他们
That's it! I'm gonna go over there and I'm confronting them right now.
所以我得讲碉堡的笑话?
So you're telling me that I have to tell racist jokes now?
对不起 我不太会圆谎
I'm just not very good at this.
我很不会骗人 我又讨厌骗瑞秋
I'm a terrible liar. I hate having to lie to Rachel.
- 但我们还不能公开   - 我知道
- But we're not ready to tell yet.      - I know.
只是从高中起 我什么事都告诉瑞秋
Ever since high school, Rachel was the one person that I told everything to.
我好怀念那种感觉
I miss that so much now.
她是我最要好的朋友
She's my best friend.
乔伊?
Joey?
- 天哪 瑞秋   - 嘿
- Oh, my God, Rachel!     - Hey!
嗨
Hi!
你怎么跑来这里?
What are you doing here?
这个嘛 我是来借这盏灯
Well, I actually came over here to borrow this lamp...
好看书
...to, um, look at my books.
看得清楚一点
You know, see them a little better. Heh.
- 太好了   - 是啊
- Okay, great. Great. Um...      - Yeah.
我在钱德的房间里是因为…
Well, what I was doing in Chandler's room is that, um...
我在帮忙打扫
...I was cleaning it.
- 他付钱请我打扫   - 是喔
- In fact, he pays me to clean it.      - Oh!
真是个赚零用钱的好办法
What a great way to make some extra pocket money.
之前我说要加班
When I said to you earlier that I was at work, um...
是指我的新工作
...I'm at my new work.
真不错 对吧?
Good enough. Right?
好 那…
Okay, well, um...
我要去看书了
I'm gonna go look at my books.
- 好 我得去忙我的新工作了   - 好
- Okay. Go get back to my new job.     - Okay.
好
Okay.
恭喜你找到这份工作
Congratulations on your new job!
天哪 她可真好骗
Man, she is really gullible.
(中央咖啡厅)
- 你们的咖啡   - 谢谢
- Here you go.     - Thanks.
- 其实我该走了   - 你确定？
- Actually, I should get going.      - You're sure?
你想留多晚我都奉陪
I can stay out as late as you want.
我说过我为什么休长假吧?
I told you I'm on sabbatical from work...
对 你说过
Yes, yes. You did. Ha-ha-ha.
- 真是的   - 又怎么了？
- Oh, man!     - What is wrong now?
我不是点这个
This isn't what I ordered.
我的人生就不能顺利一点吗?
Man! Can't anything go right in my life?
先是我的婚姻破裂 然后…
First, my marriage falls apart, and then...
我知道
I know, I know!
然后你被赶出你家 你的工作没了
You lose your apartment, then you lose your job...
你的前妻很快就再婚 现在咖啡又错了
...then your ex-wife gets married so fast! And now the coffee!
哎呀
Aah!
罗斯
Ross...
我们得谈谈  - 好
...we need to talk.     - Okay.
- 有时我觉得…  - 不…
- Sometimes I feel...     - No, no, don't.
是我要说
I'm going to talk.
我认为
I believe...
我们的美好时光
...that the sun has set...
已经落日了
...on our day in the sun.
- 什么？ - 你是个很好的人
- What?     - You're a very sweet person, Ross.
额…
Um...
但是…
Unfortunately...
我没办法再听你哀下去了
...I just don't think I can take another second of you whining!
我跟你确认一下
Let me make sure I'm hearing this right.
你要跟我结束 因为…
You're ending this with me because...
我太会发牢骚?
...I'm too whiny?
嗯
Mm.
你是说…
So you're saying...
我是这么的爱发牢骚
...I've become so whiny...
我让你…
...that I...
珍妮丝…
...annoy you...
觉得很烦
...Janice.
没错
Well, yeah!
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
- 你不要紧吧？ - 现在不要紧了
- Are you gonna be okay?     - I am now.
好吧
Okay.
- 你好   - 你好
- Hi.     - Oh, hi.
那么…
Well...
已经两人出局了
I guess, that's two out of three...
乔伊
...Joey!
- 我们得谈谈   - 好
- Dude, we gotta talk.     - Okay.
我只是想趁你听说之前告诉你
I want to tell you something before you heard it from someone else.
希望不会太奇怪
I hope this isn't too weird but, uh...
我最近跟珍妮丝交柱过
...I had a thing with Janice.
你不生气?
You're not mad?
我干嘛生气?
Why would I be mad?
因为这种事有它的道义在
Because there's certain rules about this kind of stuff.
不能追朋友的旧情人
You don't, uh... You don't fool around with your friends' ex-girlfriends...
或是…
...or, uh...
心上人 或是有亲属关系的人
...possible girlfriends or girls they're related to.
我很生气
I am mad.
但是你知道吗?我要原谅你
But you know what I'm gonna do? I'm gonna forgive you.
因为那样才叫兄弟
Because that's what friends do.
他们会原谅朋友 犯了你念的…
They forgive their friends when they do everything you just said.
- 那串禁忌   - 谢了
- All the things on the list there.     - Thank you.
但是我要你记住
But I want you to remember...
我原谅了你
...that I forgave you.
- 好   - 我还要你记住
- Okay.     - I also want you to remember...
我免费收留你
...that I let you live here rent-free.
- 好   - 我还要你记住
- All right.     - And I want you to remember...
我送你27块钱
...that I gave you 27 dollars.
无条件奉送
No strings attached!
要是你记不住
If you can't remember that...
我们应该写 我们写下来吧
...I think we should write it down. Let's write it down!